[
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "あ",
        "answer": "a"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "い",
        "answer": "i"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "う",
        "answer": "u"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "え",
        "answer": "e"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "お",
        "answer": "o"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "か",
        "answer": "ka"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "き",
        "answer": "ki"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "く",
        "answer": "ku"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "け",
        "answer": "ke"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "こ",
        "answer": "ko"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "きゃ",
        "answer": "kya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "きゅ",
        "answer": "kyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "きょ",
        "answer": "kyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "さ",
        "answer": "sa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "し",
        "answer": "shi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "す",
        "answer": "su"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "せ",
        "answer": "se"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "そ",
        "answer": "so"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "しゃ",
        "answer": "sha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "しゅ",
        "answer": "shu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "しょ",
        "answer": "sho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "た",
        "answer": "ta"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ち",
        "answer": "chi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "つ",
        "answer": "tsu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "て",
        "answer": "te"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "と",
        "answer": "to"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ちゃ",
        "answer": "cha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ちゅ",
        "answer": "chu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ちょ",
        "answer": "cho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "な",
        "answer": "na"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "に",
        "answer": "ni"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぬ",
        "answer": "nu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ね",
        "answer": "ne"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "の",
        "answer": "no"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "にゃ",
        "answer": "nya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "にゅ",
        "answer": "nyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "にょ",
        "answer": "nyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "は",
        "answer": "ha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ひ",
        "answer": "hi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ふ",
        "answer": "fu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "へ",
        "answer": "he"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ほ",
        "answer": "ho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ひゃ",
        "answer": "hya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ひゅ",
        "answer": "hyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ひょ",
        "answer": "hyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ま",
        "answer": "ma"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "み",
        "answer": "mi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "む",
        "answer": "mu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "め",
        "answer": "me"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "も",
        "answer": "mo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "みゃ",
        "answer": "mya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "みゅ",
        "answer": "myu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "みょ",
        "answer": "myo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "や",
        "answer": "ya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ゆ",
        "answer": "yu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "よ",
        "answer": "yo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ら",
        "answer": "ra"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "り",
        "answer": "ri"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "る",
        "answer": "ru"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "れ",
        "answer": "re"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ろ",
        "answer": "ro"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "りゃ",
        "answer": "rya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "りゅ",
        "answer": "ryu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "りょ",
        "answer": "ryo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "わ",
        "answer": "wa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "を",
        "answer": "wo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ん",
        "answer": "n"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "が",
        "answer": "ga"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぎ",
        "answer": "gi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぐ",
        "answer": "gu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "げ",
        "answer": "ge"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ご",
        "answer": "go"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぎゃ",
        "answer": "gya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぎゅ",
        "answer": "gyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぎょ",
        "answer": "gyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ざ",
        "answer": "za"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "じ",
        "answer": "ji"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ず",
        "answer": "zu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぜ",
        "answer": "ze"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぞ",
        "answer": "zo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "じゃ",
        "answer": "ja"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "じゅ",
        "answer": "ju"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "じょ",
        "answer": "jo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "だ",
        "answer": "da"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぢ",
        "answer": "ji"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "づ",
        "answer": "dzu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "で",
        "answer": "de"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ど",
        "answer": "do"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぢゃ",
        "answer": "ja"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぢゅ",
        "answer": "ju"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぢょ",
        "answer": "jo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ば",
        "answer": "ba"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "び",
        "answer": "bi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぶ",
        "answer": "bu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "べ",
        "answer": "be"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぼ",
        "answer": "bo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "びゃ",
        "answer": "bya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "びゅ",
        "answer": "byu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "びょ",
        "answer": "byo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぱ",
        "answer": "pa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぴ",
        "answer": "pi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぷ",
        "answer": "pu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぺ",
        "answer": "pe"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぽ",
        "answer": "po"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぴゃ",
        "answer": "pya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぴゅ",
        "answer": "pyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ぴょ",
        "answer": "pyo"
      }
    ],
    "score": {
      "correctCount": 0,
      "incorrectCount": 0
    },
    "title": "Hiragana"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "ア",
        "answer": "a"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "イ",
        "answer": "i"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ウ",
        "answer": "u"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "エ",
        "answer": "e"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "オ",
        "answer": "o"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "カ",
        "answer": "ka"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "キ",
        "answer": "ki"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ク",
        "answer": "ku"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ケ",
        "answer": "ke"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "コ",
        "answer": "ko"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "キャ",
        "answer": "kya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "キュ",
        "answer": "kyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "キョ",
        "answer": "kyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "サ",
        "answer": "sa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "シ",
        "answer": "shi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ス",
        "answer": "su"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "セ",
        "answer": "se"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ソ",
        "answer": "so"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "シャ",
        "answer": "sha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "シュ",
        "answer": "shu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ショ",
        "answer": "sho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "タ",
        "answer": "ta"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "チ",
        "answer": "chi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ツ",
        "answer": "tsu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "テ",
        "answer": "te"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ト",
        "answer": "to"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "チャ",
        "answer": "cha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "チュ",
        "answer": "chu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "チョ",
        "answer": "cho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ナ",
        "answer": "na"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ニ",
        "answer": "ni"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヌ",
        "answer": "nu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ネ",
        "answer": "ne"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ノ",
        "answer": "no"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ニャ",
        "answer": "nya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ニュ",
        "answer": "nyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ニョ",
        "answer": "nyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ハ",
        "answer": "ha"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヒ",
        "answer": "hi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "フ",
        "answer": "fu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヘ",
        "answer": "he"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ホ",
        "answer": "ho"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヒャ",
        "answer": "hya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヒュ",
        "answer": "hyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヒョ",
        "answer": "hyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "マ",
        "answer": "ma"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ミ",
        "answer": "mi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ム",
        "answer": "mu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "メ",
        "answer": "me"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "モ",
        "answer": "mo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ミャ",
        "answer": "mya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ミュ",
        "answer": "myu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ミョ",
        "answer": "myo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヤ",
        "answer": "ya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ユ",
        "answer": "yu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヨ",
        "answer": "yo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ラ",
        "answer": "ra"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "リ",
        "answer": "ri"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ル",
        "answer": "ru"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "レ",
        "answer": "re"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ロ",
        "answer": "ro"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "リャ",
        "answer": "rya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "リュ",
        "answer": "ryu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "リョ",
        "answer": "ryo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ワ",
        "answer": "wa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヲ",
        "answer": "wo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ン",
        "answer": "n"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ガ",
        "answer": "ga"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ギ",
        "answer": "gi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "グ",
        "answer": "gu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ゲ",
        "answer": "ge"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ゴ",
        "answer": "go"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ギャ",
        "answer": "gya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ギュ",
        "answer": "gyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ギョ",
        "answer": "gyo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ザ",
        "answer": "za"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ジ",
        "answer": "ji"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ズ",
        "answer": "zu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ゼ",
        "answer": "ze"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ゾ",
        "answer": "zo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ジャ",
        "answer": "ja"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ジュ",
        "answer": "ju"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ジョ",
        "answer": "jo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ダ",
        "answer": "da"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヂ",
        "answer": "ji"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヅ",
        "answer": "dzu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "デ",
        "answer": "de"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ド",
        "answer": "do"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヂャ",
        "answer": "ja"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヂュ",
        "answer": "ju"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ヂョ",
        "answer": "jo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "バ",
        "answer": "ba"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ビ",
        "answer": "bi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ブ",
        "answer": "bu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ベ",
        "answer": "be"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ボ",
        "answer": "bo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ビャ",
        "answer": "bya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ビュ",
        "answer": "byu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ビョ",
        "answer": "byo"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "パ",
        "answer": "pa"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ピ",
        "answer": "pi"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "プ",
        "answer": "pu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ペ",
        "answer": "pe"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ポ",
        "answer": "po"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ピャ",
        "answer": "pya"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ピュ",
        "answer": "pyu"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ピョ",
        "answer": "pyo"
      }
    ],
    "score": {
      "correctCount": 0,
      "incorrectCount": 0
    },
    "title": "Katakana"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "おはよう",
        "hint": "ohayou",
        "answer": "Hello,\nGood Morning"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "こんにちは",
        "hint": "konnichiwa",
        "answer": "Hello,\nGood Afternoon"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "こんばんは",
        "hint": "konnbanwa",
        "answer": "Hello,\nGood Evening"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "ありがとう",
        "hint": "arigatou",
        "answer": "Thanks"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "どういたしまして",
        "hint": "douitashimashite",
        "answer": "You're Welcome"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "〜です",
        "hint": "~ Desu",
        "answer": "~ is."
      },
      {
        "prompt": "〜をください",
        "hint": "~　wo kudasai",
        "answer": "Please give me ~."
      }
    ],
    "score": {
      "correctCount": 0,
      "incorrectCount": 0
    },
    "title": "Basic Phrases"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "一",
        "hint": "ichi",
        "answer": "One"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "二",
        "hint": "ni",
        "answer": "Two"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "三",
        "hint": "san",
        "answer": "Three"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "四",
        "hint": "shi, yon",
        "answer": "Four"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "五",
        "hint": "go",
        "answer": "Five"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "六",
        "hint": "roku",
        "answer": "Six"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "七",
        "hint": "shichi, nana",
        "answer": "Seven"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "八",
        "hint": "hachi",
        "answer": "Eight"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "九",
        "hint": "kyuu",
        "answer": "Nine"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "十",
        "hint": "ju",
        "answer": "Ten"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "百",
        "hint": "hyaku",
        "answer": "Hundred"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "千",
        "hint": "sen",
        "answer": "Thousand"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "万",
        "hint": "man",
        "answer": "Ten Thousand"
      }
    ],
    "score": {
      "correctCount": 0,
      "incorrectCount": 0
    },
    "title": "Numbers"
  }
]
